You are not going to have significantly
higher quality of life as a billionaire.
Also, it's important to realize that
aging is the biggest problem you've got.
So, most of the needs that we actually
have can be satisfied with very basic
resources. As I got more pro in the
industry, I realized that there is no
clinical proof that show longevity
benefit for someone who is already fit
and does not have dramatic unhealthy
habits. And finally, the most important
biomarker you can change today is your
psychological age. This is something
that you can change by strategically
deceiving yourself that you are going to
live a very long [snorts] life and you
are going to behave as a younger
individual. So, right now, there is
nothing you can do except [music] for
what
I like to refer to as do what your
mother told you. And the best strategy
anyone listening can pursue
is actually getting into this field and
learning.